[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "You tell me, what'd he do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "-NONE-", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "And -- no, no, no, you tell me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Michigan Avenue"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What does it feel like taking (inaudible) yesterday, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Big difference, Piers, than we did within Michigan Avenue downtown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "And what kind this train generally, is this massive cold burst now putting on all electric grids in that area?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, specifically with the train passengers, they ran into a snow grip that the train believably couldn't get through so they were stranded for.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "How's your derriere feeling out for about 48 hours in the freezing close standing on your feet, Ted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "My face is worst than my derriere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What was this you feel like to be in these extreme cold temperatures?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, Piers, it is obviously cold here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Is there sense of anger of what JetBlue does or was it basically all they could do in these circumstances?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "You know, there is probably some anger from passengers just because of all of the flights that have been canceled.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["JetBlue"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hawaii"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "CD", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Has this ever happened if all recorded freezing temperatures before at the same time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "You know, it has and even for Hawaii because you have (inaudible) and you have, you know, mountains that are 14 thousand, 60 thousand feet high.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Australia", "England"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "New York City, Buffalo all talking about 50 degrees by Saturday, Atlanta to 60 and even in the Minneapolis to 32, how about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "TO", "CD", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "CD", ",", "WRB", "RP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, I just got back from Australia watching England debacle playing cricket, and it was a 114 degrees there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "LOCATION": ["New York City", "Buffalo", "Atlanta", "Minneapolis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "``", "UH", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "But what is your sense, Chad, about what is going on here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Yeah, I've heard a lot of chatter about, \"Oh look at this global warming.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "What are you doing right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, we're taking care of all of the animals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Has it been that dangerous for them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Neither the zoo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "What is the best advice for what you do in this kind of situation if this deep freeze continues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "You know, if you have animals that are outdoors, the best thing that you can do is bring those animals inside.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "And the pandas, are they the ones are enjoying this the most?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "RBS", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "The pandas are definitely enjoying it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "What do you think is really going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Well, Piers, you know, it's really important to remember that while the long term trend is global warming, that the climate is warming, I prefer the term climate change because it gives a little bit of a more accurate sense of exactly what's happening, long term that the client is changing and growing warmer, but that can mean that in short term trends, some places will get warmer, some places will get colder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "To those who remain resolutely skeptic about all these and say, there's no such thing as global warming, there's no science that really supports it, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "WP", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "CC", "VB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "I mean it's - there are people that are advancing in agenda that it's not going to do with science I think in that case because, of course, the science is overwhelming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", ",", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Are they right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, one of the things that's important to remember too is that in many cases, though not all, climate change is not necessarily causing these storms to happen but can increase the severity of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Well, but to take action and then be proven wrong than to take no action and not be proven wrong, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Well, what do you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I think he's an idiot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Do you understand what he did --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 259, "question": "And you tell me, what did he do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "No, no, no, you tell me, you tell me why is he held captive --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "They haven't released -- they haven't released any reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Rodman"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "ORGAN: I mean, Senator McCain, the problem at all this is, it sounds shockingly naive at best or worse, he's become a kind of a propaganda tool for the North Korean regime, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJS", "CC", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well absolutely I mean for him to say, do you know what he did, obviously they had feed Mr. Rodman some lying about the person which is, you know, is the whole thing is a -- as I say in one respect it's kind of side show where the guy that's not too bright, that's looking for something to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McCain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "It's a assessment I've had frankly since the Presidential campaign.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["American Troops"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Well talking of Fallujah there were reports as with Al-Queda as we take in control in parts of Fallujah, what does this tell you about the reality of the situation in Iran there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "It tells me because we didn't leave the force behind not to fight to influence and to help and train and assist and do all the things that American Troops could do and not fight anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Fallujah", "Fallujah", "Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$6 billion", "$6 billion"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Finally, and it's certain that there's ongoing battle over unemployment benefits, where are you sitting on this issue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Well, I'd like to find a way to pay for the $6 billion this cost, it's impossible for me that to believe that we can't find $6 billion in order to fund this rather than just increase the debt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "And what are the key things you think the people should embrace as they reach the 50 milestone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, this is kind of an aspirational time of life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara", "Mike Wallace"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "But what kind of inspiration of somebody like Barbara not just to your generation but to all future generations really, of women in the media, women working anywhere in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, she's a really good example of the -- it used to be these exceptional people like Barbara or Mike Wallace in our industry who could continue to be at the top of the majors for an entire career.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barbara"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bryant Gumbel"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Your life calling is that it's both an opportunity and -- Oh, yes, what am I going to do for 40 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "ORGAN: One thing you could, you recently be back with Bryant Gumbel and return in Today Show in glory.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Could you see yourself making a dramatic comeback into the breakfast TV world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "So pretty impressive right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Welcome, Sherri, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I'm not twerking, I'm a little tired and, you know, I like to twerk.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sherri"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "How do you battle the demons up there on your shoulder?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, number one, I'd say you have to forgive yourself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "So what do I do about the fact that I'm allergic to Kale?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "OK, what -- now, being allergic is one thing and you can't stand it is another.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "So, which one is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WDT", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "No, I'm not really allergic to it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What about having inside the Big Mac and large fries I have for lunch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "There's your problem again, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Big Mac"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Do you as to what this is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Hello Piers (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "What's your thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "It's probably you at the moment, Piers, but I'm probably close behind you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Are you still running up a pretty large hill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I should think that we've got to the point where we got to the top of the hill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "According to the CDC one out of every eight preschoolers is obese in the US high in African- American and Hispanic kids, what have you found to be the most effective way of talking to kids in particular and their parents about how to change habits?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well that's a really good point you made.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CDC"], "LOCATION": ["US"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "And that prompts the obvious question, how do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Well, mainly because most people used pig ingredients, sorry, pork parts in surgery and stuff like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "You know, so are you a cannibal then, Jamie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jamie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nigella"]}, "docId": "140107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "What is your thought?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I love Nigella.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]